https://ecards.co.uk/privacy-policy

All Jokes
Tongue & Cheek (Our Fav.)
Business
Misc.
Yes / No
Sports
Privacy Policy The eCards.co.uk Privacy Policy .
After its recent aquisition, eCards.co.uk is now owned and managed by Web-Clubs Digital Ltd - eCards.co.uk is therefore used in accordance with the group privacy policy which can be found here :
https://www.web-clubs.co.uk/privacy-policy/
In addition to our group privacy policy, eCards.co.uk Terms of Use set out some important terms that apply to your use of the eCards website at www.ecards.co.uk.
In addition to our group privacy policy, this addendum details some important privacy terms that apply to your use of the eCards website at www.ecards.co.uk.
eCards.co.uk Specific Privacy Policy Addendum
Use of information and your consent
We can only collect your information for lawful and stated purposes. We can only use your personal information for the purposes stated in this Privacy Policy. By providing us with your personal information,you consent to us processing this information in one or more of the ways described in this Privacy Policy.
Where we collect your personal information:-
ECards
If you ask us to send an eCard (the "Services"),we need your name and email address and the name and email address of the person you are sending the eCard to. You must have the consent of the recipient to give us their name and email address and also any personal information you disclose in your message to them.
Providing this information is optional,but we cannot send an eCard on your behalf without you providing us with this information.
If you insert an image,including a photograph,into an eCard from a source other than the Website,you must have the consent of the person whose image it is and/or the owner of that image to use that image before it is inserted into an eCard and to allow us to store the image for use by you in future eCards from time to time.
In the case of images of children who are not capable of giving consent,you should ensure that the relevant consent is obtained from the child's parent or guardian.
By inserting an image into an eCard from a source other than the Website, you confirm that you have obtained the necessary consents referred to in the above paragraph.
We do not accept any liability whatsoever for any image inserted by you into an eCard from a source other than the Website without the consent of the person,parent or guardian and/or owner (as the case may be).
If you are a recipient of an eCard then before you can open your eCard we will ask you to agree to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, by doing this you consent to us collecting, using and storing your personal information (including any image of you) in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Customer service
In order for us to respond to your questions or concerns,we may need personal information like your name,address and email address. This information is used to answer your questions as completely and thoroughly as possible.
Information that we collect automatically:-
There are many kinds of cookies,but these are the ones you need to know about…
As well as the personal information that you provide us with,we will also use information obtained about you automatically from cookies (files which are sent by us to your computer). The main reason we use cookies is to gather information on how you and other users use our Website and Services.
For example,cookies will tell us whether you viewed the Website with sound or with text on your last visit and will allow us to count the number of unique and return users to the Website.
We may access cookies stored on your computer when you visit our Website in future or when you open an email from us.
We are able to do this by including web beacons (also known as clear GIFS or web bugs) in our emails.
If you want to delete any cookies that are already on your computer,please refer to the instructions for your file management software to locate the file or directory that stores cookies.
Our cookies will have the file name “__utmb.txt,__utmc.txt,__utmz.txt,vis.txt,PHPSESSID.txt,lang.txt,user_cookie.txt”.
For more information about deleting and controlling cookies visit www.aboutcookies.org. Alternatively,please refer to your browser manufacturer's instructions by clicking "Help" in your browser menu. Please note that by deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our Website or send an eCard.
Our web beacons do not store additional information on your computer but,by communicating with our cookies on your computer,they can tell us when you have opened emails from us.
If you object to web beacons,we recommend that you follow the instructions for deleting existing cookies and disabling future cookies.
We will still know how many of our emails are opened and we will automatically receive your IP address,a unique identifier for your computer or other access device; but we will not identify you as an individual.
Third party cookies
Please be aware that when you leave the Website via a link to a third party website,that third party website may use cookies and you will need to refer to the third party's privacy or cookie policy.
Web Clubs Digital Limited is a company incorporated in England and Wales with Company number: 11832568.
Changes to this policy
We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page – when we do, we will also revise the last updated date featured here:
23/09/2020
eCards.co.uk
eCards.co.uk is an online Greeting Card site. We offer free digital eCards that are sent via email,facebook and twitter.
The eCards are completely FREE to send and we have thousands of cards to choose from.
© 2019 eCards.co.uk - now part of Web-Clubs Digital Ltd. - Web-Clubs.co.uk
8 Temple Square,
Aylesbury,
Bucks,
HP20 2QH
